Hello friends, I am Mohammad Arshad, a
certified financial planner. I
welcome you all to my YouTube channel.
Friends, I have been
associated with the insurance industry for the last 11 years and
every week I bring you a video so that it becomes
very easy for you to understand the insurance plan and you can get the
right insurance plan for yourself and your family.
Friends, ICICI Lombard has come up with a new
health insurance plan. The
name of this plan is Elevate. Friends, the
tagline of this plan is Power of
Infinity. Its sign is also Infinity,
which has no limit. Friends,
this plan is really like magic.
Limitless. Friends, in today's video we are going to
understand this plan in detail. So this
video is going to be very interesting. Do
not skip it at all and
watch it till the end. So let's start.
Friends, there are
five Infinitys in this new product of ICICI Lombard which you
need to know. The first is
Infinity. When your sum assured gets exhausted,
then your sum assured will be reset unlimited times.
Friends, the fourth is Infinity.
You might not have heard of this before. Cumulative Bonus
means your policy will increase every year 100%
every year up to an
infinite Rs. 10 lakh policy. If you are
not using it, then it will become Rs. crore in 20 years.
And last but not the least is Jump
Start Advance which gives you infinite
tenure from 18 years to 125 years. If we
talk about the policy tenure in this plan, then
this plan can be taken by paying premium for one, two or three years together.
If we
talk about the sum assured in this plan, then you have been given the option of Rs. 5 lakh, 75 lakh, 10 lakh, 15 lakh, 20 lakh, 25 lakh,
1 crore, 3 crore unlimited
sum assured. If we
talk about the family size, then
this plan can be taken for two adults plus three children.
Also, one more special thing is that
dependent child can be covered in this plan
till the age of 30. If we
talk about the room in this plan, then you have been given a single private
AC room.
Talking about AYUSH treatment, it
is covered up to Rs 200,000. If we
talk about day care treatment in this plan, then it is also
covered up to the sum assured. If we
talk about domestic treatment in this plan, then it is also
covered up to the sum assured. Just keep in mind
that the treatment must be for at least three days.
If we talk about donor expenses, then
it is also covered up to the sum assured. If we
talk about domestic road ambulance, then it is
also covered up to the sum assured. Friends,
in this plan you are also covered for sero-gas
up to Rs 5 lakh. Along with this,
you are also covered for various surgeries
up to the sum assured. If we
talk about refill benefit in this plan, then it is 100%
off all the time. Unlimited number of times.
If we talk about guaranteed cumulative bonus in this plan, then
it is 20 per every year, whether there is a
claim or not and it goes up to 100%.
Friends, I would also like to tell you here
that you  By paying some extra premium,
you are also given a wellness program in this Infino plan,
through this you can get a
discount of up to 30% in your renewal premium.
Friends, till now we have talked
about all the inbuilt features provided in this plan. Now let's
talk about the advance.
Friends, ICICI Lombard has
brought so much flexibility and
so much choice in this new product that you would not have even imagined.
Let's understand friends. The
first advance is that
after taking Infino, you can pay the advance
once during your entire policy period, that is, as long as
you are running the policy.
Suppose you have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh
and your bill comes to Rs 20
lakh, 25 lakh or 50 lakh, then you do
not need to worry, the company will pay your entire bill.
Many times it happens that some
critical incident occurs which we would
not have even thought of, so once our claim is settled,
Infino
is taken. Friends, the next advance is Power Booster.
Friends, you might not have heard of such an advance before.  It is
completely different in the insurance industry. It is a revolution and will create a
stir in the entire industry. Friends,
after taking this advance, you will get a guaranteed
community bonus of 100% every year. If you have taken an
Infakill policy, then the next
year it will be 20 lakhs, then 30 lakhs, then
40 lakhs. Similarly, it will keep increasing, after 20 years it will be
2 crores, after 30 years it will be 3
crores, in this order, there is
no limit and that too every year whether you
claim or not. So friends, isn't it
different? Friends, after this comes the next advance,
Jump Start Advance. Friends,
with this advance, you will be able to cover your pre-existing
diseases like asthma, diabetes, hypertension,
obesity after just 30 days,
whose normal waiting period is 3 years.
Friends, after this, the next advance is
Claim Protector. Friends,
after taking this advance, all your non-pay by items will be
covered up to two times.
Friends, after this comes the turn of
Evasion Protector Advance.
After taking this advance, your sum assured increases every year.
According to inflation,
friends, after this comes the turn of
domestic air ambulance.
After taking this advance, your air ambulance will also be covered up
to some
extent. Friends, after this the next advance is
room
modification. Do you understand? After taking this advance,
you can also upgrade your room
from a single standard AC room to any room
and you can also downgrade your room
like twin sharing room.
Friends, after this comes the turn of dependent
accommodation benefit. After taking this advance,
if you have to be admitted to the hospital,
then all your dependents
get Rs 1000 per day for a maximum of 10 days.
Friends, next comes the matter of
maternity benefit. Through this advance, you
can cover your maternity. If we
talk about its limit, then there is
maternity cover up to 10 percent of your age limit, whose
maximum limit is up to ₹ 1 lakh. Its waiting
period is 2 years. Friends, if you have
also taken newborn baby cover, then the
newborn baby cover is 9 days.
It will last up to 2 times the delivery sum. For
vaccination expenses,
you can avail cover up to 1% of your time suit or a maximum of ₹100. Friends, here
I would like to inform you that if you
want to reduce the waiting period for maternity cover, you also get this advance.
In this, you can reduce the waiting period from 2 years to
one year. Friends,
after this, the next advance is Nursing at
Home. Friends, many times after leaving the hospital,
we need nursing at home.
After taking this advance, you can charge ₹100 per
day for the next 10 days of nursing.
If you hire a qualified nurse,
you
can also claim it on a reimbursement basis. Friends,
after this, the next advance is Durable Medical
Equipment. Friends, many times
after hospitalization, you need to purchase some medical equipment at home,
such as
wheelchair, bed, etc. You can also avail the benefit of this.
Covered up to ₹100 lakh, friends.
Compassionate Cover: Friends,
if you have taken this advance, then if you are
admitted in the hospital for more than 10 days,
the company gives you Rs. 0,000 cash. Friends, you must
also be wondering how many advances are there in this policy.
Indeed, there are a
lot of advances given in this policy, that is why I
said that this plan is very
flexible. The next advance is
health checkup. Friends, after taking this advance,
you can get a
health checkup done once a year up to a maximum of Rs. 000 of your time shot.
Friends, the next advance
is B Fit. After taking this,
you can cover your OPD. If you
want to know about it in detail, then I will
bring a video for you very soon on this B Fit rider. Friends, after this, the next
advance is tele consultation. If you have
taken this advance, then you can
consult a doctor unlimited number of times
through tele call or video call.
After this, the next advance is Value Copayment.
Friends, if you want to reduce your premium, then for this
you
can choose a payment ranging from 10% to 50%.  The
payment is basically through claim
sharing. This means that
you will have to pay the percentage of your chosen claim from your own pocket.
After this, the next advance is Network
Advantage Advance. Friends, insurance
companies have identified their preferred partner
networks. If you
choose a preferred partner network hospital
for treatment, you get a discount of 10% on the premium.
However, if you
get treatment somewhere other than these hospitals,
then you have to pay 20%.
After this, the next advance is Personal
Accidental Cover. Accidental
death and permanent disability are covered under this advance. The
limit of this advance is up to Rs 50 lakh and
you can take this advance even before the age of 65.
After this, the next advance is
Critical Illness Rider. After taking this advance,
20 critical illnesses are covered.
If this critical illness is diagnosed,
then you are given a lump sum amount. The
limit for this is Rs 50 lakh, that is, up
to Rs 50 lakh.  You can avail cover under this rider.
Friends, let's now discuss the waiting period provided in this plan.
If we
talk about the initial waiting period, it is
30 days. If we talk about the waiting period for specific diseases,
it is 24 months.
Friends, the waiting period for diabetes, hypertension and cardiac
conditions is 90 days. The
waiting period for critical illness is also
90 days. The waiting period for PD is 36
months. The waiting period for rheumatic surgery is
24 months. The
waiting period for maternity is 24 months, which can be reduced to
12 months. Similarly,
you can also reduce the waiting period for PD to 30 days. Friends, now
some discounts are also given in this plan, let's
talk about them.
First of all, it comes to the credit score discount.
Friends, if your CIBIL score is good,
then the company gives you a discount of up to 15%.
After this, it comes to the long term discount.
Friends, if you  If you pay two years'
premiums at once, you get a 10%
discount, and if you pay three years' premiums at once, you
get a 15% discount.
Next is the early renewal discount.
Friends, if you pay your renewal
premium 30 days before the due date, the
company gives you a 30% discount.
Friends, next comes the
wellness discount, which you get up to 30%.
For this, you have to perform some wellness
activities. You can download ICICI
Lombard's Oil Tech Care application,
where activities are
counted, and you
get a discount based on that. Friends, I hope
you understand this plan well.
Still, if
you have any questions about this plan, you
can type your query in the comment box.
If you want to buy this plan or
want to buy the best health insurance plan for your family,
I would like to inform you that we provide
health insurance policies and
all related services on an all-India basis.
We also provide general assistance at the time of claim.
You can follow
us there as well as given in our box
and in the last I request all of you to
like this YouTube video of ours and share it as much as possible and also do
not forget to turn on the notification bell so that you keep getting information about
new videos of new plans coming in the future.
Friends, you
took out your precious time and watched this video,
thank you very much for that, see you soon
[Music]
[Music] [
Music]